ratedapartments.com 2012-10-05

# Privacy Policy - RatedApartments.com

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 

**Rated Interactive Media** and its associated websites is strongly committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal and financial information secure. The Personal Information that **RatedApartments.com** collects from you shall be obtained, processed and transmitted in compliance with applicable data protection legislation. We take full responsibility for ensuring that proper security measures are in place to protect your information and store the information in secure databases at secure addresses to prevent unauthorized access. **Rated Apartments** reserves the right to update information published on the site at any time including (but not exclusive to): rates, descriptions and photographs. **Rated Apartments** does not guarantee condition or suitability of any product or service as advertised on its website. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 

Information collected by **RatedApartments.com** and how it is used: **RatedApartments.com** only collects the necessary personally identifiable information in order to respond to your requests for our customized products and services. Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, physical address, e-mail address, phone number, birth date, and any other information that itself identifies or when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual. This website does not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. **RatedApartments.com** and its service partners use your personally identifiable information to operate the sites and services and to inform you of new features, services, and products from **RatedApartments.com** and its affiliates. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 

**RatedApartments.com** may also carefully select other companies to send you information about their products or services which are related to the site's service but are not necessary to its operation (an "Extended Service"). If **RatedApartments.com** intends to use personally identifiable information for an Extended Service, the **RatedApartments.com** site will provide you with the ability and requisite instructions to decline this service. You may also stop the delivery of informational or promotional mail from **RatedApartments.com** by following the instructions on the mail. 

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
